dayriffer.com 2012-05-27

# Privacy Policy | DayRiffer

Dayriffer.com is committed to protecting online user privacy. In order to ensure your privacy while using this website, we collect your information only in the manner and for the purposes described below.

This "Privacy Policy" contains the privacy practices governing dayriffer.com's collection, use, and disclosure of personal information. Capitalized terms used herein shall have the same meaning as designated in the dayriffer.com Terms of Service located at <http://dayriffer.com/terms-of-use>, unless otherwise specifically defined in this Privacy Policy. All references herein to "we" or "us" refer to dayriffer.com. All references to the "Site" refer to our website located at [http://dayriffer.com](http://%20dayriffer.com/).

## Children

Our Site is not directed towards children 13 years of age or younger and we do not knowingly collect any information from children 13 years of age or younger through the Site.

## Collected Information

### Personally Identifiable Information

Although you may generally use our Site without providing us with any personally identifiable information, for some Site applications or services, we may collect certain types of personally identifiable information, including: name, postal address, e-mail addresses, birth date, and phone number. This type of information is only collected from you voluntarily; we will never gather or store such information without your knowledge and consent. Examples of where we might gather such information from you: when you sign up to receive e-mail updates or newsletters about the Site, our products, or services; to allow you to register or update your individual profile on the Site; to help personalize the Site for you; or to allow you to provide feedback, or ask a question. In some situations, you will need to provide some or all of the above-described personally identifiable information in order for certain personalized features of the Site to function properly (e.g., company and product email alerts).

We may use such information to contact you about our products, company or other related marketing or promotional purposes.

We do not share personally identifiable information collected at this Site with third parties, except for the limited instances noted below. The exceptions are:

  * We may share your information with our agents who assist us in administering the Site and various programs and promotions. They can only use the information to administer our Site, services, and products. These agents are required to keep your information private and secure.
  * If you opt-in (either at the time of providing personally identifiable information, or at a later time) to have us share your information with our partners for the purpose of receiving information from our partners and other companies.
  * We may also disclose personally identifiable information if we are required to comply with laws, or if in our good faith judgment, such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, to respond to any claims, or to protect the rights of dayriffer.com, its customers and the public.
  * In the event of an acquisition of all or part of dayriffer.com by another company, or in the event that dayriffer.com was to sell or dispose of all or a part of its business, the acquirer would have access to the information maintained by dayriffer.com, which could include personally identifiable information, subject to applicable law. Similarly, information may be transferred as part of a reorganization or insolvency proceeding.

We may on occasion combine information we receive with outside records or Site usage information to enhance our consumer profiles for our own marketing and development purposes (in accordance with this Privacy Policy).

Although we use reasonable efforts to maintain the privacy of your personally identifiable data and information, due to technological limitations, and the risk of unlawful interceptions and accessing of transmissions and/or data, we cannot completely assure you, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable data and information, and any other electronically communicated information, will be absolutely confidential.

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We also collect and store non-personally identifiable information, such as visitor traffic, page hits, Site referral information, browser information, downloads, and general Site use information through typical Internet data collection tools, such as web beacons, cookies, and embedded web links.

This Site may use cookie and tracking technology. A "cookie" is a tiny file that your browser places on your computer's hard drive, which acts to identify your computer. Cookie and cookie tracking technology is useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help tailor the Site to visitors' needs and help customize the Site for visitors. For example, we may use cookies to store your Site preferences, usage patterns, and other information so that the Site will function better for you on subsequent visits. The Site may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other similar purposes. Personally identifiable information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information (as discussed above), cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregated cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. If you choose to reject the Site's cookies, some areas of the Site may not function properly or may not be accessible.

### Automatically Collected Log Information

In addition to the information discussed above, when you visit the site we may collect and store the following information in our logs for each browser request. We may use such information for development and marketing purposes (we will not use IP addresses externally except as set forth above):

  * the date and time
  * the originating IP address
  * the type of browser and operating system used (if provided by the browser)
  * the URL of the referring page (if provided by the browser)
  * the object requested
  * completion status of the request
  * pages visited

The tools we use do not obtain personal information about you and cannot obtain information from your hard drive or pass on a computer virus. We use non-personal information to better understand the use of this Site, to improve and revise the Site, and to track interest.

## Correspondence

We maintain and review e-mail correspondence that you send to us. We will use the personally identifiable information disclosed in the e-mail. Because such correspondence contains information that is not transmitted through the operation of our web site, it is not subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## Information Processing

We process information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners, provided that we will not reveal such information except in accordance with this privacy policy.

## Demographic Information and Surveys and Polls

We may ask for demographic or profile (age, gender, household, interests, etc.) information in a survey/poll or at registration. This information is used to assist us in tailoring the site, our communications, and our services and products to visitors and consumers. We may share aggregated demographic and survey information, as opposed to individual information, with third parties. You always have the option of not responding to any questionnaire, survey, or poll.

## Security, Opting Out, and Access to Information

Dayriffer.com uses commercially reasonable efforts to keep personally identifiable information secure. Only authorized dayriffer.com employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information and only to help dayriffer.com administer its promotional programs and the site.

If you have signed up to receive newsletters and email from us, we will make every effort to have all such communications allow you to opt-out of further such communications. To unsubscribe from our mailing list(s), please email info@dayriffer.com.

If enabled on the site, you may visit your account settings page to delete your account and/or information. You can also contact us at info@dayriffer.com to request deletion of your account and/or information. Please note that any information that we have may remain in back-up storage for some period of time after your deletion request. This may be the case even though no information about your account remains in our active user databases. Also please note that log files are not affected by account deletion requests.

## Links to Other Internet Websites

This Site may include hyperlinks or data that can take you to a third party website, document, file, or other materials. These third party sites will contain their own, different privacy provisions. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting Personal Information to those sites. We are not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through these other web sites, and we expressly disclaim any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure.

## Amendments

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy periodically. Any amendments made to this Privacy Policy will be considered effective ten (10) days after the amendments are posted on the site.

## Sale of Assets

In the event that there is a merger, consolidation, reorganization, or another company acquires the stock or assets of dayriffer.com, we reserve the right to include information among the assets to the changed corporate structure.

## Terms

Reference is made to the Terms of Service for the Site which shall apply to this Privacy Policy as if set forth in full herein. You may wish to review them at <http://dayriffer.com/terms-of-use>.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions about our services or Privacy Policy, please contact dayriffer.com, 130 West Union Street, Pasadena, CA 91103 or send an e-mail to info@dayriffer.com.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on October 19, 2010.
